(Raj:)No, it's time to put on some R. Kelly
and suck face.
(Penny:)Oh, wow, is the evening over.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
Wait, wait, wait. That's my mommy
and daddy calling from India.
(Raj(as a ringing noise is heard):)I want you to meet my parents.
Wait, meet them?
Hello, Mommy, Daddy. Good to see you.
How are you? I'm not drunk.
- Why would you say that?
- Just making conversation.
Mommy, Daddy, I want you to meet
my new squeeze, Penny.
(Penny:)I am not your squeeze.
There is no squeezing.
I can't see her. Center her in the frame.
(Raj:)Here you go. Cute, huh?
(Mrs Koothrappali:)She's not Indian.
(Dr Koothrappali:)So she's not Indian.
The boy's sowing some wild oats.
No, no, no, there's no sowing,
no squeezing and no sucking face.
What if he gets her pregnant?
Is this hotsy-totsy who you want
as the mother of your grandchildren?
(Raj:)What right do you have
to pick whom I can have children with?
(Dr Koothrappali:)Look, Rajesh, I understand,
you're in America...
...you want to try the "local cuisine."